Eugenics Record Office Records 1670-1964 Mss.Ms.Coll.77
American Philosophical Society
- Microfilm
  - Microfilm Reels (Box Microfilm: 1-70)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822183 (Box Microfilm-56)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822184 (Box Microfilm-56)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822196 (Box Microfilm-56)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822197 (Box Microfilm-56)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822198 (Box Microfilm-57)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822199 (Box Microfilm-57)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822219 (Box Microfilm-57)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822220 (Box Microfilm-57)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822574 (Box Microfilm-57)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822575 (Box Microfilm-57)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822576 (Box Microfilm-58)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822577 (Box Microfilm-58)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822938 (Box Microfilm-58)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822939 (Box Microfilm-58)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822940 (Box Microfilm-58)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822941 (Box Microfilm-58)
    - Persons File, 1822942 (Box Microfilm-59)
    - Persons File, 1822943 (Box Microfilm-59)
    - Persons File, 1822944 (Box Microfilm-59)
    - Persons File, 1822945 (Box Microfilm-59)
    - Persons File, 1822946 (Box Microfilm-59)
    - Persons File, 1823033 (Box Microfilm-59)
    - Persons File, 1823034 (Box Microfilm-60)
    - Persons File, 1838383 (Box Microfilm-60)
    - Persons File, 1838384 (Box Microfilm-60)
    - Persons File, 1838385 (Box Microfilm-60)
    - Persons File, 1838386 (Box Microfilm-60)
    - Persons File, 1838387 (Box Microfilm-60)
    - Persons File, 1838508 (Box Microfilm-61)
    - Persons File, 1838509 (Box Microfilm-61)
    - Persons File, 1838510 (Box Microfilm-61)
    - Persons File, 1838511 (Box Microfilm-61)
    - Persons File, 1838512 (Box Microfilm-61)
    - Persons File, 1838513 (Box Microfilm-61)
    - Persons File, 1838719 (Box Microfilm-62)
    - Fitter Family Studies, 1839026 (Box Microfilm-62)
    - Fitter Family Studies, 1839027 (Box Microfilm-62)
    - Fitter Family Studies (item 1); Midget Schedules (item 2), 1839272 (Box Microfilm-62)
    - Midget Schedules (item 1); Trait Files (item 2), 1839273 (Box Microfilm-62)
    - Trait Files, 1839274 (Box Microfilm-62)
    - Persons File, 1839309 (Box Microfilm-63)
    - Persons File, 1839310 (Box Microfilm-63)
    - Persons File, 1839311 (Box Microfilm-63)
    - Persons File, 1839456 (Box Microfilm-63)
    - Persons File, 1839457 (Box Microfilm-63)
    - Persons File, 1839458 (Box Microfilm-63)
    - Persons File, 1839459 (Box Microfilm-64)
    - Persons File, 1839460 (Box Microfilm-64)
    - Trait Files, 1839524 (Box Microfilm-64)
    - Trait Files, 1839525 (Box Microfilm-64)
    - Trait Files, 1839526 (Box Microfilm-64)
    - Trait Files, 1839527 (Box Microfilm-64)
    - Trait Files, 1839672 (Box Microfilm-65)
    - Trait Files, 1839673 (Box Microfilm-65)
    - Trait Files, 1839674 (Box Microfilm-65)
    - Trait Files, 1839675 (Box Microfilm-65)
    - Trait Files, 1839676 (Box Microfilm-65)
    - Persons File, 1839699 (Box Microfilm-65)
    - Persons File, 1839700 (Box Microfilm-66)
    - Persons File, 1839860 (Box Microfilm-66)
    - Persons File, 1839861 (Box Microfilm-66)
    - Persons File, 1839862 (Box Microfilm-66)
    - Persons File, 1839863 (Box Microfilm-66)
    - Trait Files, 1839870 (Box Microfilm-66)
    - Trait Files (item 1); Trait Card Boxes (item 2), 1839871 (Box Microfilm-67)
    - Trait Card Boxes, 1839872 (Box Microfilm-67)
    - Trait Card Boxes, 1839873 (Box Microfilm-67)
    - Trait Card Boxes, 1839874 (Box Microfilm-67)
    - Persons File, 1844894 (Box Microfilm-67)
    - Persons File, 1844895 (Box Microfilm-67)
    - Persons File, 1845028 (Box Microfilm-68)
    - Persons File, 1845511 (Box Microfilm-68)
    - Persons File, 1845512 (Box Microfilm-68)
    - Persons File, 1845513 (Box Microfilm-68)
    - Persons File, 1845514 (Box Microfilm-68)
    - Persons File, 1845515 (Box Microfilm-68)
    - Persons File, 1845679 (Box Microfilm-69)
    - Persons File, 1845680 (Box Microfilm-69)
    - Persons File, 1845681 (Box Microfilm-69)
    - Persons File, 1845682 (Box Microfilm-69)
    - Persons File, 1845683 (Box Microfilm-69)
    - Persons File, 1845684 (Box Microfilm-69)
    - Persons File, 1845685 (Box Microfilm-70)
    - Persons File, 1845804 (Box Microfilm-70)
  - Index to Microfilm
    - Detailed Studies File ("D") 1765326-1765329
    - Field Worker Files 1765329, 1769006-1769008, 1769149-1769151, 1769424-1769427, 1769581-1769583, 1769687, 1769689, 1769819, 1769858, 1787242-1787243, 1787365-1787366, 1788113, 1822181-1822184, 1822196-1822199, 1822219-1822220, 1822574-1822577, 1822938-1822941
    - Fitter Family Studies 1839026-1839027, 1839272
    - Index 1 (surname, locality, trait) 1683047-1683048, 1683266-1683278, 1683352-1683360, 1683485-1683494, 1683554-1683562, 1683650-1683654, 1683711-1683717, 1683836-1683846, 1683878-1683880, 1684023-1684033, 1684082-1684091, 1711418-1711423
    - Index 3 (locality, surname, trait) 1683445-1683452, 1683541-1683546, 1683635-1683638, 1683706-1683709, 1683894-1683902, 1684047-1684052, 1711515-1711522
    - Index 4 (locality, trait, surname) 1712058-1712063, 1712222-1712226, 1712320-1712324, 1753703-1753713, 1753734, 1753756-1753761, 1753870-1753873, 1753875-1753881, 1753926-1753928, 1765703-11765705, 1765863-1765872, 1765963-1765967, 1766233-1766242, 1766308-1766310, 1766373-1766375, 1786795-1786800, 1787023-1787027, 1818495-1818499
    - Marriage Files ("M") 1764930-1764931, 1765324-1765326
    - Midget Schedules 1839272-1839273
    - Persons File 1822942-1822946, 1823033-1823034, 1838383-1838387, 1838508-1838513, 1838719, 1839309-1839311, 1839456-1839460, 1839699-1839700, 1839860-1839863, 1844894-1844895, 1845028, 1845511-1845515, 1845679-1845685, 1845804
    - Record of Family Traits 1749616-1749619, 1749908-1749915, 1752823-1752826, 1753068-1753081, 1753089-1753104, 1753327-1753338, 1753500-1753501, 1753666-1753667, 1763181-1763187, 1763380-1763388, 1763459-1763470, 1763696-1763707, 1763779-1763788, 1763964-1763972, 1764604-1764613, 1764693-1764701, 1764783-1764791, 1764927-1764931
    - Record of Family Traits (Index) 1711553-1711558, 1711742
    - Special Studies ("W") 1711742-1711745
    - Trait Card Boxes 1839871-1839874
    - Trait Files 1839524-1839527, 1839672-1839676, 1839870-1839871